<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.babe.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0</project_license>
  <name>Babe</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Babe</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Babe</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Babe</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Babe</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxBabexx</name>
  <summary>Babe is a tiny music collection manager</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">El Babe és un gestor de col·leccions de música</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Babe is een kleine beheerder van een muziekverzameling </summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">O Babe é um pequeno gestor de colecções de música</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Babe — малесенька програмка для ведення збірок звукових даних</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxBabe is a tiny music collection managerxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Babe will handle your whole music collection by retrieving semantic information from the web.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Babe gestionarà tota la vostra col·lecció de música recuperant la informació semàntica des del web.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Babe zal uw gehele muziekverzameling behandelen door het ophalen van semantische informatie van het web.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Babe подбає про усю вашу музичну збірку, скориставшись семантичними даними з інтернету.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxBabe will handle your whole music collection by retrieving semantic information from the web.xx</p>
    <p>Just relax, enjoy and discover your new music </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Simplement relaxeu-vos, gaudiu i redescobriu la vostra música</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Rustig maar, geniet en ontdek uw nieuwe muziek</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Simplesmente descanse, divirta-se e descubra a sua nova música</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Просто розслабтеся і насолоджуйтеся вашою музикою</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxJust relax, enjoy and discover your new musicxx</p>
    <p>Use the Chrome extension to collect your favorite music videos from online streaming services like YouTube or Vimeo. Babe uses youtube-dl, so all the supported sites by it are also supported by Babe</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Usa l'extensió de Chrome per a recopilar els vostres vídeos musicals preferits des de serveis de transmissió en línia com YouTube o Vimeo. El Babe fa servir «youtube-dl», de manera que tots els llocs admesos també seran compatibles amb el Babe</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Gebruik de Chrome-extensie om uw favoriete muziekvideo's uit online streamingservices, zoals YouTube od Vimeo te verzamelen. Babe gebruikt youtube-dl, dus alle daarmee ondersteunde sites worden ook door Babe ondersteund</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Use a extensão do Chrome para obter os vídeos da sua música favorita a partir de serviços de transmissão 'online', como o YouTube ou o Vimeo. O Babe usa o youtube-dl, pelo que todos os serviços suportados pelo mesmo serão também suportados no Babe</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Скористайтеся розширенням Chrome для збирання ваших улюблених відео зі служб потокового відтворення в інтернеті, зокрема YouTube і Vimeo. Babe використовує youtube-dl, тому у Babe забезпечено підтримку усіх сайтів, підтримку яких передбачено у youtube-dl.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxUse the Chrome extension to collect your favorite music videos from online streaming services like YouTube or Vimeo. Babe uses youtube-dl, so all the supported sites by it are also supported by Babexx</p>
    <p>Babe has a main playlist where you can drag and drop tracks, artists, albums and custom playlists to be played or put on queued. </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Babe té una llista de reproducció principal on podreu arrossegar i deixar anar pistes, artistes, àlbums i llistes de reproducció personalitzades per a reproduir-les o posar-les a la cua.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Babe heeft een hoofdafspeellijst waar u tracks, artiesten, albums en eigen afspeellijsten naar kunt slepen en laten vallen om te worden afgespeeld of in de rij gezet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Babe tem uma lista de reprodução principal para a qual poderá arrastar e largar faixas, bem como os artistas, álbuns e listas personalizadas a reproduzir ou a colocar em fila de espera.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">У Babe передбачено основний список відтворення, до якого ви можете перетягувати пункти композицій, виконавців, альбомів та нетипових списків відтворення для негайного відтворення або додавання до черги відтворення.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxBabe has a main playlist where you can drag and drop tracks, artists, albums and custom playlists to be played or put on queued.xx</p>
    <p>Create your own playlists and search for music based on semantic queries.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Creeu les vostres pròpies llistes de reproducció i feu una cerca de música basada en les consultes semàntiques.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Maak uw eigen afspeellijsten en zoek naar muziek gebaseerd op semantische zoekopdrachten.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Crie as suas próprias listas de reprodução e procure por músicas com base em pesquisas semânticas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Створюйте власні списки відтворення та шукайте музику на основі семантичних даних.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxCreate your own playlists and search for music based on semantic queries.xx</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Send your music to your phone.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Envia la música al telèfon.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Stuur uw muziek naar uw telefoon.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Envie a sua música para o seu telefone.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Надсилайте музику на ваш телефон.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSend your music to your phone.xx</li>
      <li>Add moods to your music.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Afegeix estats d'ànim a la música.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Voeg stemmingen toe aan uw muziek.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Adicione estados de espírito à sua música.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Додавайте настрої для музичних творів.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxAdd moods to your music.xx</li>
      <li>Edit your file metadata with the help of the internet.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Edita les metadades del fitxer amb l'ajuda d'Internet.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Bewerk uw bestandsmetagegevens met de hulp van het internet.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Edite os meta-dados dos seus ficheiros com a ajuda da Internet.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Редагуйте метадані ваших файлів, використовуючи дані з інтернету.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxEdit your file metadata with the help of the internet.xx</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://babe.kde.org/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=babe</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=Babe</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image type="source">https://babe.kde.org/img/release-1.0/playlists-view.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image type="source">https://babe.kde.org/img/release-1.0/albums-view2.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image type="source">https://babe.kde.org/img/release-1.0/playlist-mode.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image type="source">https://babe.kde.org/img/release-1.0/mini-mode.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <provides>
    <binary>babe</binary>
  </provides>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
</component>
